HEROLD L. KIRALY

FRONT END DEVELOPER



kiraly-h@pm.me

heroldkiraly.com

ABOUT ME

Since 2013 I have experimented at a hobby level to code video games, I have tried many different kinds of career paths and just recently gained a passion for Front End Development. Doubled down and decided to learn a large variety of web technologies, and its only the beginning.

SKILLS

- · Web Design
- HTML5/CSS3
- JavaScript
- SCSS (Sass)
- React JS
- Git/Github work flow
- Strong communication skills

EXPERIENCE

OWNER/OPERATOR

Reno Kings LLC

2020 - 2021

- Direct communication with clientele
- Management of resources/partners
- General business operations

OFFICE MANAGER

Glower Designs & Construction

2019 - 2020

- Management of invoices/projects
- File layout creation & 3D modeling
- Client communication regarding project questions

EDUCATION

CODECADEMY FRONT END COURSE

Advanced course from basic HTML to React JS

2022

HARVARD CS50

General Computer Science Course

2022

LIFE INSURANCE AGENT

AIG

2018 - 2019

- Gathering target leads and contacting possible clients via phone/email
- Build presentations to review personal performance
- Internal office communication between co-workers for strategy sharing